# **Eric Kongkaew**

www.linkedin.com/in/erickongkaew erickongkaew@gmail.com • https://www.erikmoxley.com/ (978) 935-8860 • Greater Boston, MA 01851

#### **SUMMARY**

Passionate Software Engineer with 6+ months of experience working professionally as a developer creating unique websites and web apps for local and nation-wide businesses. 12+ years as a Former Manager of Pharmacy and Retail, Project Manager, and Assistant Manager of Operations in the Pharmaceutical industry with past experiences of high-level management in planning, resourcing, and execution of major projects.

#### **TECHNOLOGIES AND TOOLS**

HTML5 • CSS3 • Sass • Bootstrap • JavaScript • GitHub • Version Control • VSCode • Netlify • Heroku MySQL • Express • ReactJS • NodeJS • NPM • NextJS • Atlassian • Jira • Asana

# PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

# **PHOENIX AFTERGLOW - Burlington, MA**

# Software Developer

Mar 2022 - Present

- Design, develop and establish user-friendly, responsive, SEO optimized live websites and web-based applications for local and nation-wide businesses within industries such as: Specialty Trade Contractors, Retailers, Restaurants, Health & Wellness, Hospitality, Real Estate, Home Improvement, Travel, etc
- Maintain 30+ current clients' products through feature requests, bug fixes, integrations and enhancements
- Integrate back-end eCommerce into multiple websites with full shopping cart and payment functionalities
- Revamp company procedures and workflows including revising company's HR policies, SOPs and onboarding, building high-end work PCs, upgrading software, and introducing industry relevant tools for increased productivity and functionality during each project's life cycle
- Technologies, tools and other skills used: HTML5, CSS3, JavaScript, JQuery, Bootstrap, Sass, GitHub, React, NextJS, NodeJS, Express, MySQL, PHP, Microsoft Office, Agile/Scrum, Asana, Google Analytics, FTP, Adobe Creative Suite

# WALGREENS BOOTS ALLIANCE INTERNATIONAL/CO. – Greater Boston, MA

# Manager of Pharmacy and Retail

Sep 2007 - May 2019

- Managed 25+ direct reports including Assistant Managers, Supervisors, Pharmacy Managers, Technicians, etc.
- Coached multiple Management Trainees through passing company university work assignments each focal point: customer care, reducing shrink and new age digital adoption of tech and software where key ideas and strategies were later implemented in the company's future initiatives and the mentorship also resulted in their promotions to Managers of Pharmacy and Retail for the area
- Involved in creating efficient training procedures, templates, guidelines and tools used district wide which led to increased leadership engagement, improved on-boarding and an average employee retention increase by 25%
- Exceeded customer Net Promoter Score (75%+) & Rx patient care (78%+) targets 2 years in a row

#### **District Project Manager**

- Provided overall project management, strategy and oversight on major transformation project in merger with U.K.
   company that resulted in promotion to Manager of Pharmacy and Retail
- Led district leadership team of 8 to implement new cosmetic lines such as No7/S&G into 8 locations in the area
- Participated in ~12 district meetings involving scope, cost, and timing to meet company and stakeholder expectations
- Managed communication, scheduling, budget of 2,600 hours, issue & risk managements, and other PMI functions
- Communicated with at least 8 vendor teams, small contractors and mid to large sized suppliers located on and offsite
  to accomplish project results

## **Assistant Manager of Operations / Supervisor**

- Managed 15+ direct reports ranging from Pharmacy Tech Trainees to Customer Service Associates
- Utilized Kronos to maintain time cards and bi-weekly payroll; Workforce for scheduling, PTO and overall budgeting

# **PROJECTS**

# **COMPANY FULL STACK INPUTS PAGE**

Oct 2021

**Full-Stack Web Development –** HTML, CSS, JavaScript, Express, NodeJS, MySQL, Express Validator **LIVE:** https://erikmoxley.github.io/fs-test-ek

SOURCE: https://github.com/ErikMoxley/fs-test-ek

- Front end built with HTML, CSS, JavaScript deployed on GitHub Pages using their domain
- Using a Node back end, submitted POST goes through ExpressJS deployed on Heroku

Uses a MySQL database to receive POST requests and MySQL Workbench for admin to check data sent

NEXTJS BLOG Aug 2021 – Nov 2021

Front-End Web Development - NextJS, CSS, JavaScript, React Router Dom, Netlify Forms

LIVE: https://moxleydevblog.netlify.app

**SOURCE:** https://github.com/ErikMoxley/moxleydevblog

- Personal and developer blog page built with NextJS by Vercel, The React framework
- Markdown files are converted to posts using slug components sorted by date
- Contact page uses Netlify Forms CMS to manage and accept submissions, email notification once received

#### MEDIAN AND AVERAGE INPUTS PAGE

Jan 2022

Front-End Web Development - HTML, CSS, JavaScript

LIVE: https://erikmoxley.github.io/fe-test-inputs

SOURCE: https://github.com/ErikMoxley/fe-test-inputs

- Simple HTML form that displays back the average and median to the user from 3 inputs
- Front end validation. HTML integrated 'step' only allows positive integers to be used on submit

# **EDUCATION AND CERTIFICATION**

• Zero to Mastery Academy • Udemy – Remote • www.github.com/erikmoxley Aug 2019 – Sep 2021 Software Engineering • Web Development • HTML5, CSS3, JavaScript, Bootstrap, Sass, ReactJS, NextJS, NodeJS, Git

Learn Engage Advance Perform (LEAP) – Manchester, NH

May 2016

Business Management • Pharmaceutical Industry • WBA University for Drug Store Managers

• GROW InsideOut Development and Coaching - Greater Boston, MA

Nov 2017

GROW model is one of the most used coaching models for Agile coaching and frameworks

## **ADDITIONAL**

Volunteering:

<ul> <li>VFW Foundation – Haverhill, MA</li> </ul>	2018
Cystic Fibrosis – Haverhill, MA	2016 – 2018
American Diabetes Association – Waltham, MA	2016
Team Walk for Cancer Care - Lowell, MA	2015
Community Action Council - Bedford, MA	2021